<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Servers>
    <ServerGroup Name="Ravenhearst" Logo="" Description="Can you survive the terror?">
        <Server Name="Ravenhearst 11" Logo="">
		    <DownloadMode>Clone</DownloadMode>
            <Downloads>
                <Download>https://github.com/JaxTeller718/Ravenhearst_11_6.git</Download>
            </Downloads>
            <Description>
			Stable release of Ravenhearst for 2.6b14. Currently on v11.0.0b8
			
			Future v10 updates will automatically post here. Title will not change. These include both client and server files. For direct files head to our discord.
			
			The ORIGINAL Hardcore mod from A14 brings its mixture of slower grind and difficulty to A20 with more features and changes than ever before!
			
			Do you enjoy a more methodical and slower based progression system? Do you feel the base game is too fast, other mods seem uneven or just not catering to that specific hardcore taste that you want?
			
			Ravenhearst is the mod for you! Featuring hundreds of balancing changes and tweaks, new recipes, new deco, new enemies like Night Terrors, new vehicles, Tier 5 radiated pois, Journal Quest line with end game rewards, expanded EVERYTHING, Learn by Doing, old restored vanilla features like upgrades to blocks, and hundreds of more features and changes Ravenhearst has enough fright and terror to satisfy even the most toughest of players.
		
			Patch Notes for v11.0.0b8
				
Updated to v2.6(14)
Updated RH Core
Updated Quartz
Updated Gears
Updated Score
Reverted Air Drops to our original Air Drops
Added smell to all of our food
Added Bundles to our Meats
Removed Beehives and rebalanced around the Apiary
Adapted Workstation and Seed Crafting Skills to Ravenhearst
Added new 2.5 maps generated with Modded RWG DLL for Road Fixes not in Vanilla
Adjusted Snow Zombie spawns
Fixed incorrect display value on bowl of honey
Added Sonja Fallout Armor
Updated TMOCore
Added Socket to Rare Automotive Group
Fixed Brewery Issues
Completed Journal now scraps to KP
Completed Journal sell value increased
Fixed Tier 5 Skill icons and descriptions
Aligned all zombie XP to new vanilla formatting
Removed Posters and Coolers from Crooked Deco. If you see any other deco that looks wrong let me know and we can remove them.
Swapped Stoner and AK-47
Adjusted Loot Timers for Gas Barrel and Multiple Gas Barrels
Removed duplicate wheel recipe
Lowered price of Crucible
Fixed smell on fish tacos
Fixed traps skill book recipe
Removed extra scrap brass pallet bundle recipe
Adjusted recipes of some weapons
Increased degradation drain of Guitar slightly
Increased chance of bee and honey events on stumps and probability on trees
Increased crop fuel counts in Apiary to 100
Removed spoilage from Goldenrod and Chrysanthemum
Removed duplicate empty jar recipe
Fixed various Sonja armor errors
Converted all Beehive quests to Apiary
Removed Dew Gatherer, Filter and Tarp from recipes and added to loot
Reduced probability of Radiated Screamer spawn on Scout groups
Shifted all of our Gamestages
    New Gamestages
	25 = 50
	50 = 100
	100 = 300
	300 = 500
	500 = 700
	700 = 1000
This will move up spawning of those groups to the new shifted gamestage. We can push these further out if necessary
Increased recipe costs of electric relay, posts and timer made in workbench
Added electric posts, relay and timer to electric table as secondary recipe with reduced recipe costs (less than vanilla original cost)
Fixed and changed all instances of biome mushrooms giving back vanilla mushroom seeds when destroyed instead of our seeds
Updated Old West POI's
Updated FNS POI's
Lowered Dire Wolf Sound
Enhanced Lock/Unlock Icons Visual and Audio
Anvils can now be scrapped
Gave Drop Models to many food and drink items
Lowered Health on RH Runners (Air Drops etc)
Adapted RH drinks to use Empty Jar Return Settings
Tuned down chance of honey event in stumps
Reduced Honey received to 2 from 3
Added Bees event to Stumps to collect Bees
Cleaned up Old West POI Zombie nulls
Reduced Heatmaps on Personal WorkBench, Farm Table, Table Saw and Tanning Rack
Backpack Slots Opening Too Soon Fix - Zakov
Adjustments for Over Spawn of Old West Towns (Requires New Map)
Adjustments for Cities and Towns Map Wide (Requires New Map)
Quality Fixes - Zakov
Fixed Weapons not scrapping into their proper parts
Salt recipe changed. Survival Campfire 20 seconds24 halite, chem station 12 halite 10 seconds
Removed extra Raw Meat Bundle Recipe
Removed Jar returns from Pies
Added new Speedloader - Zakov
Adjustments to the Splash Logo - Zakov
Replaced Old Action Skills with New Coded Version - Zakov
Ensured .dlls for Zakov Action Skills are included
Updated Speedloader - Zakov
Updated Score
Added Glass Breaking Sound when a Jar is Consumed
Rebalanced zombie biome spawning
Fixed ability to store loot in Bench Outputs - Zakov
Fixed incorrect quality settings in Score
Update Score
Removed TMO Modlets
Fixed Cardboard Box
Updated Active Ingredients - Zakov
Removed duplicate setting folder
Added Storms
Updated Old West POIs
Various hand model fixes for cans and bottles
Updated ZZTongs POI Pack
Added Double G Zombie Classic Reimagined
Added Crater POI Pack
Updated Atmospheric Storms


		    	Found a bug or poi stability issue and wish to let us know?  Head to Discord https://discord.gg/YBHD9f3 and post your logs.

			</Description>
           	
           	<Version>Release</Version>
            <EAC>Disabled</EAC>
			<Author>JaxTeller718</Author>
			<Admin>JaxTeller718</Admin>
			<Discord>https://discord.gg/YBHD9f3</Discord>
			<Twitter>https://twitter.com/JaxTeller718</Twitter>
			<Donate>https://www.paypal.me/FrankCirabisiJr</Donate>


        </Server>
    </ServerGroup>
</Servers>
